isportconnect.com 2019-09-04

# Privacy Policy - iSportConnect

1. **Privacy  Policy  
**1.1 This privacy policy (“ **Policy** ”) sets out the basis on which we will process any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us or which is provided to us by a third party acting for you or on your behalf, in relation to events we organise and when you visit our website. This Policy also describes what cookies we use on our website and provides you with information on how you can disable cookies. This Policy does not apply to information collected by third parties, including through any application or content that may link to or be accessible from our website. **  
** 1.2 In this Policy, “ **we** ” or “ **us** ” refers to **iSportconnect UK Ltd.** being a limited liability company registered in England and Wales with registration number 08025767 and whose registered office is at Unit 3, Temple Place, 247 The Broadway, Wimbledon, SW19 1SD.  
1.3 Please read this privacy policy carefully – by accessing or browsing this website and network (the “ **Services** ”), you confirm that you have read, understood and agree to this privacy policy in its entirety. If you do not agree to this privacy policy in its entirety, you must not use the Services.  
1.4 This privacy policy was last updated on August 7th, 2019. Please check back regularly to keep informed of updates to this privacy policy.

2. **Who we are**  
2.1 This social networking website is made available to you by iSportconnect UK Ltd. We respect your right to privacy and will only process personal data you provide to us in accordance with the EU General Data Protection Regulation 2018, the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003 and other applicable privacy laws.  
2.2 We are a controller for the purposes of the data protection laws. This means that we are responsible for deciding how to hold and use personal data about you. iSportconnect UK Ltd is required under data protection laws to notify you of the information contained in this policy.  
2.3 If you have any questions about how we collect, store and use personal data, or if you have any other privacy-related questions, please contact us at [ray@isportconnect.com](mailto:ray@isportconnect.com).

3. **An important note about children**  
3.1 We do not and will not knowingly collect information from any child under the age of 18. If you are under the age of 18, you must not use any of the Services.

4. **The personal data we collect about you**  
4.1 When you access and browse the Services (including when you submit personal data to us through data entry fields on the Services), we may collect the following information from you: (i) Your name; (ii) Your postal address (this is optional); (iii) Your phone and e-mail details; (iv) Your employment details; and (v) Any other personal data that you choose to upload to or post on the Services, including blogs, photographs, messages, hobbies and interests and other personal details.  
4.2 We may process analytical data about your use of our website (“ **usage data** “). The usage data may include your geographical location, browser type and version, operating system, referral source, length of visit, page views and website navigation paths. The source of the usage data is Google Analytics. This usage data may be processed for the purposes of analysing the use of the website and services. The basis for this processing is monitoring and improving our website and services (when in our legitimate interests). If you do not wish us to track your usage data, you can opt-out by enabling the ‘Do Not Track’ option in your browser. You can also control analytics by installing this browser add-on by Google: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.

5. **How we may store and use your information**  
5.1 We (or third party data processors acting on our behalf) may collect, store and use your personal data listed above for the following purposes:  
a. to make the Services available to you and to provide you with content which is tailored to your individual tastes;  
b. to complete any purchases you make through the Services and to provide you with services that you request;  
c. to further develop and improve the Services;  
d. to maintain and support any customer account that you have with us;  
e. to include (or to permit the inclusion of) advertising within the Services of our own and third party products, services and promotions that we or they think may interest you;  
f. where you have given us your consent, to contact you (including by SMS and e-mail) with invitations, services and opportunities which we think may interest you; and  
g. where you have given us your consent, to disclose your personal data to carefully chosen third parties so that they may contact you (including by SMS and e-mail) with products, services and promotions which they think may interest you.  
5.2 Other than as set out in this privacy policy, we will not disclose, sell or rent your personal data to any third party unless you have consented to this. If you do consent but later change your mind, you may contact us and we will cease any such activity.  
5.3 However, if a third party acquires all (or substantially all) of our business and/or assets, we may disclose your personal data to that third party in connection with the acquisition.  
5.4 We may also disclose your personal data where we are required to do so by applicable law, by order of a court, by a governmental body or by a law enforcement agency. We may also disclose your personal data in the context of investigating or reporting any issue arising in connection with activity by you or content supplied or purporting to be supplied by you, to you or on your behalf that we reasonably believe could be unlawful or otherwise in breach of our terms of service.

6. **Technology Licensor disclosures**  
6.1 We may also disclose your personal data to the business that provides us with technology infrastructure and hosting services for the Service (the “ **Technology Licensor** ”). The Technology Licensor will use your personal data in order to check that you are using the Services in a way that complies with applicable law, does not infringe the rights of any third party, to maintain and improve the infrastructure and hosting services that it provides to us, to serve advertising within the Services of third party products, services and promotions that it thinks may interest you and otherwise in accordance with its privacy policy.

6.2 For iSportconnect TV ([https://tv.isportconnect.com](https://tv.isportconnect.com/)) the Technology Licensor is SportRadar AG and the information for their privacy policy and cookie usage can be found below:  
<https://sportradar.com/about-us/privacy/>  
<https://sportradar.com/about-us/cookies/>

7. **International transfers**  
7.1 We may transfer personal data that we collect from you to third parties (including the Technology Licensor) located in countries that are outside of the European Economic Area where necessary to exercise, or in connection with, the uses of your data described above. Please be aware that countries which are outside the European Economic Area may not offer the same level of data protection as the United Kingdom, although our collection, storage and use of your personal data will continue to be governed by this privacy policy.

8. **Retaining and deleting personal data**  
8.1 Section 8 sets out our data retention policies and procedure, which are designed to help ensure that we comply with our legal obligations in relation to the retention and deletion of personal data.  
8.2 Personal data that we process for any purpose or purposes shall not be kept for longer than is necessary for that purpose or those purposes.  
8.3 Personal data relating to iSportconnect UK Ltd. events will be retained for a maximum period of three years.  
8.4 Notwithstanding the other provisions of this Section 8, we may retain your personal data where such retention is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject, or in order to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another natural person.

9. **Amendments  
**9.1 We may update this Policy from time to time by publishing a new version on our website.  
9.2 We will take reasonable steps to make you aware of any material changes to this Policy, but we also recommend you that you revisit this page from time to time to keep informed of our current privacy practices.

10. **Your rights**  
10.1 In this Section 10, we have summarised the rights that you have under data protection law. Some of the rights are complex, and not all of the details have been included in our summaries. Accordingly, you should read the relevant laws and guidance from the regulatory authorities for a full explanation of these rights and can find out more information [here](https://ico.org.uk/for-organisations/guide-to-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr/individual-rights/).  
10.2 Your principal rights under the data protection law are as follows (and we’ve provided some further details about each below):  
a. the right to access;  
b. the right to rectification;  
c. the right to erasure;  
d. the right to restrict processing;  
e. the right to object to processing;  
f. the right to data portability;  
g. the right to complain to a supervisory authority; and  
h. the right to withdraw consent.  
10.3 You have the right to confirmation as to whether or not we process your personal data and, where we do, access to the personal data, together with certain additional information. That additional information includes details of the purposes of the processing, the categories of personal data concerned and the recipients of the personal data. Providing the rights and freedoms of others are not affected, we will supply to you a copy of your personal data. The first copy will be provided free of charge, but additional copies may be subject to a reasonable fee.  
10.4 You have the right to have any inaccurate personal data about you rectified and, taking into account the purposes of the processing, to have any incomplete personal data about you completed.  
10.5 In some circumstances you have the right to restrict the processing of your personal data. Those circumstances are: you contest the accuracy of the personal data; processing is unlawful but you oppose erasure; we no longer need the personal data for the purposes of our processing, but you require personal data for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims; and you have objected to processing, pending the verification of that objection. Where processing has been restricted on this basis, we may continue to store your personal data. However, we will only otherwise process it: with your consent; for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims; for the protection of the rights of another natural or legal person; or for reasons of important public interest.  
10.6 In some circumstances you have the right to restrict the processing of your personal data. Those circumstances are: you contest the accuracy of the personal data; processing is unlawful but you oppose erasure; we no longer need the personal data for the purposes of our processing, but you require personal data for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims; and you have objected to processing, pending the verification of that objection. Where processing has been restricted on this basis, we may continue to store your personal data. However, we will only otherwise process it: with your consent; for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims; for the protection of the rights of another natural or legal person; or for reasons of important public interest.  
10.7 You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data on grounds relating to your particular situation, but only to the extent that the legal basis for the processing is that the processing is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by us or by a third party. If you make such an objection, we will cease to process the personal information unless we can demonstrate compelling legitimate grounds for the processing which override your interests, rights and freedoms, or the processing is for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims.  
10.8 You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data for direct marketing purposes (including profiling for direct marketing purposes). If you make such an objection, we will cease to process your personal data for this purpose. You’ll be able to opt-out from emails we send you by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of those emails.  
10.9 You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data for scientific or historical research purposes or statistical purposes on grounds relating to your particular situation, unless the processing is necessary for the performance of a task carried out for reasons of public interest.  
10.10 To the extent that the legal basis for our processing of your personal data is: a. consent; or b. that the processing is necessary for the performance of a contract to which you are party or in order to take steps at your request prior to entering into a contract, and such processing is carried out by automated means, you have the right to receive your personal data from us in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format. However, this right does not apply where it would adversely affect the rights and freedoms of others.  
10.11 To the extent that the legal basis for our processing of your personal information is consent, you have the right to withdraw that consent at any time. Withdrawal will not affect the lawfulness of processing before the withdrawal.  
10.12 You may exercise any of your rights in relation to your personal data by emailing [ray@isportconnect.com](mailto:ray@isportconnect.com), in addition to the other methods specified in this Section 10.

11. **Cookies  
**11.1 This website uses cookies to collect information about you. Cookies are small data files which are placed on your computer by this website and which collect certain personal data about you. This enables us to tailor our service offering (including the website) to provide you with products and services which are more relevant to your individual tastes. However, you may change your website browser settings to reject cookies, although please note that if you do this it may impair the functionality of the Services. As each website browser is different, please visit your browser’s “Help” menu to learn how to change your cookie preferences.

12. **Security  
**12.1 Whilst we take appropriate technical and organizational measures to safeguard the personal data that you provide to us, no transmission over the Internet can ever be guaranteed secure. Consequently, please note that we cannot guarantee the security of any personal data that you transfer over the Internet to us.

13. **Third party sites and sharing options  
**13.1 This website also contains links to other third party websites over which we have no control. Please note that this privacy policy applies only to the personal data that we collect through this website and we cannot be responsible for personal data that third parties may collect, store and use through their independent websites.  
13.2 The sharing tools provide website visitors with the ability to share content with websites and social networks that are not affiliated with iSportconnect UK Ltd. By clicking on those links or sharing that content, you may be sharing personal information with these third parties.
